Guide to the Yale Medical Journal Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Medical Journal records
1894-1911
RU 520
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
The records consist of the constitution, amendments to the constitution, reports, correspondence, minutes, and journals documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Medical Journal.
Yale Medical Journal
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 40 (YRG 40), Records of Yale clubs, societies, and organizations.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Biographical / Historical
The Yale Medical Journal, a Yale student publication, was established in 1894.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of the constitution, amendments to the constitution, reports, correspondence, minutes, and journals documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Medical Journal.
Yale Medical Journal; College student newspapers and periodicals; Journalism, Medical; Medicine; Yale University -- Students
- Records, 1894-1911; Accession 19ND-A-408
  - Constitution, catalog, journal, minutes, 1894-1907 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constitution with amendments passed, 1897 May (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Report of Committee, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1907 Nov (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1908 May-Jul (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1908 Aug-Oct (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1908 Nov-Dec (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1909 Jan-May (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1909 Jun-Dec (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1910 Jan-Dec (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1911 Jan (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous advertisements (Box 1, Folder 12)